My life is
usually a quiet
one. I work
from home as
a freelance writer,
which means my
days are spent
in the comforting
silence of my
apartment, punctuated only
by the gentle
clatter of my
keyboard and the
occasional meow of
my cat, Luna.
I value peace
and tranquility above
almost everything, finding
that it's essential
for my creativity
and overall well-being.
That's why I
chose this particular
apartment complex –
it was known
for its strict
noise policies and
respectful residents. Or
so I thought.
Enter Mark, my
new neighbor. He
moved in a
few weeks ago,
and ever since,
my peaceful existence
has been shattered.
It started subtly,
with slightly louder-than-usual
TV sounds in
the evenings. I
figured he was
just settling in
and would eventually
adjust the volume.
But then came
the parties. Loud,
thumping bass that
vibrated through my
walls, drunken shouts
and laughter that
echoed through the
hallways, and music
that seemed to
penetrate every corner
of my apartment.
I tried to
be reasonable. The
first time, I
knocked on his
door and politely
asked him to
turn it down.
He apologized profusely,
claiming he didn't
realize how loud
it was and
promised it wouldn't
happen again. But
it did. Again
and again. Each
time, the same
empty apologies, followed
by more noise.
I started documenting
everything: dates, times,
descriptions of the
noise, and my
attempts to contact
him. I even
invested in a
decibel meter to
accurately measure the
sound levels, which
consistently exceeded the
complex's regulations. I
complained to the
apartment management, but
they were slow
to respond. They
sent him a
few warnings, but
the noise persisted.
It was clear
that Mark had
no respect for
his neighbors or
the rules of
the complex. The
constant noise was
affecting my work,
my sleep, and
my sanity. I
was constantly on
edge, dreading the
next eruption of
sound. That's when
I decided that
if the apartment
management wasn't going
to do anything,
I would have
to take matters
into my own
hands. I started
formulating a plan,
a way to
give Mark a
taste of his
own medicine, but
in a way
that was both
subtle and undeniable.
I knew I
couldn't stoop to
his level and
create a disturbance
myself. Instead, I
would use his
own love of
loud music against
him. My plan
began with researching
sound frequencies. I
discovered that certain
frequencies are particularly
irritating to the
human ear, even
at relatively low
volumes. I then
purchased a small,
inconspicuous device that
could emit these
frequencies. It looked
like an ordinary
air freshener, but
it was capable
of producing a
range of sounds
undetectable to most
people, but incredibly
annoying to those
sensitive to them.
Next, I waited
for the perfect
opportunity. It came
a few days
later when Mark
hosted another one
of his infamous
parties. As the
music blared and
the bass thumped,
I activated my
device. I placed
it strategically near
the shared wall
between our apartments,
ensuring that the
irritating frequencies would
be directed towards
his living room.
At first, nothing
seemed to happen.
The party continued
in full swing.
But then, I
noticed a subtle
shift. People started
looking uncomfortable, their
faces contorted in
slight frowns. The
conversations became less
animated, the laughter
less frequent. Some
guests started leaving
early, citing headaches
or feeling unwell.
Mark, too, seemed
affected. He kept
adjusting the volume
of the music,
trying to find
a sweet spot
that would appease
his guests. But
no matter what
he did, the
atmosphere remained tense
and uncomfortable. Eventually,
the party fizzled
out, much earlier
than usual. The
next morning, I
saw Mark outside,
looking tired and
haggard. He glared
at me as
I walked past,
but I simply
smiled sweetly and
wished him a
good day. He
didn't say a
word. The parties
stopped after that.
Mark still played
his music, but
at a much
more reasonable volume.
And whenever I
heard it getting
too loud, I
would simply activate
my device, and
the noise would
quickly subside. He
never knew what
was causing the
discomfort, but he
clearly understood that
something was making
his music less
enjoyable. My life
has returned to
its peaceful state.
The silence in
my apartment is
once again a
source of comfort
and inspiration. And
every time I
hear a faint
thump from Mark's
apartment, I smile,
knowing that I
have the power
to restore the
peace. He may
have thought he
could disrupt my
life without consequence,
but he learned
the hard way
that even the
quietest of neighbors
can have their
revenge.